Mine.
Ningninghou: So here's the thing.
Ningninghou: Let's survey the area first.
Ningninghou: Nan, you take this circle, okay?
Nan Nandu: Okay.
Ningninghou: This circle.
Jin Jinliang: Then I'll take that circle.
Ningninghou: You take that circle.
Ningninghou: And you?
Ke Ke'ai: I'll search around the dining table.
He Heda: Then I'll take this circle.
Countdown started
Dingdingdang: There's something under the table.
Li Liwo: There's a noise!
Li Liwo: Intruder!
Li Liwo: Someone's here!
Ah!
Nan Nandu: Where did he come from?
Nan Nandu: Don't touch me!
Li Liwo: Someone's here!
-30s
He Heda: You just wait.
Li Liwo: What?
Li Liwo: Who's there?
Li Liwo: Over there!
Li Liwo: What's that sound?
-30s
Ah!
Li Liwo: What? What is this?
Li Liwo: What is this thing?
Li Liwo: Who's there? What is this thing?
Li Liwo: It's not human!
-30s
Dingdingdang: Come on, let's just be bold for once!
Dingdingdang: We're definitely failing this round anyway!
Dingdingdang: Hurry!
Li Liwo: Something's wrong!
-30s
Li Liwo: It's over, this room is full of people.
Li Liwo: It's a Zombie Siege!
Li Liwo: Geez.
Time's up
Challenge failed
Please remain where you are.
The countdown will restart in three minutes.
Ningninghou: What about the one up there?
Nan Nandu: I checked up there, nothing.
Dingdingdang: What about behind the curtains?
Ke Ke'ai: I checked behind the curtains, nothing.
He Heda: Wait, did you guys not find a single bottle?
Ke Ke'ai: I found some.
Nan Nandu: Found several.
Jin Jinliang: There are no bottles over here.
Dingdingdang: No bottles at my spot by the dining table.
Nan Nandu: The bottles I found are for something else.
Jin Jinliang: I really don't have any bottles here.
Ningninghou: Okay.
He Heda: Okay.
Ningninghou: So, I suspect someone saw something.
Ningninghou: But they aren't telling us.
Ningninghou: So for this round,
Dingdingdang: Really?
Ningninghou: Let's swap places.
Nan Nandu: Sounds good.
Ningninghou: Okay?
He Heda: Sure, let's start once we're ready.
Jin Jinliang: Okay, let's start.
Countdown started
Li Liwo: Someone's here!
Li Liwo: Intruder!
Li Liwo: Who's there?
Li Liwo: What the heck keeps making that noise here?